Guide to the Betsy Wade Files on the Newspaper Guild of New York WAG.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- The Newspaper Guild convention delegates election: Committee for a Strong and United Guild; Representative Assembly Slate-leaflets, May 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- The Newspaper Guild convention delegates election: Membership Slate-drafts of campaign literature, May 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Unit elections: Membership Slate-leaflets, October 16-October 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Unit elections: Rank and File Coalition-leaflets, October 16-October 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Unit elections: Membership Slate-finances, notes, October 16-October 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- (New York Times) Unit referendum on unit clarification: leaflets, October 30, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- (Daily News) Unit election, referendum on appeal of election, and re-run of election: Leaflets, petitions, correspondence, October 1980, November 1980, March 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Local election: Membership Slate-correspondence, December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Local election: Membership Slate-leaflets, December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Local election: Dues Reduction Party-leaflets, December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Local election: Membership Slate Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer Search Committee-notes and memos, December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- (1980) Local election dispute: legal documents and correspondence, December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- The Newspaper Guild convention delegates elction: Membership Slate leaflets, May 1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- The Newspaper Guild convention delegates election: Membership Slate correspondence, memos, strategy notes, May 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- The Newspaper Guild convention delegates election: Democratic Coalition Slate leaflets, May 1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- International Executive Board Election: Membership Slate correspondence and memos, September 1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- International Executive Board Election: Unity Slate and Rank and File Slate leaflets, September 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- International Executive Board Election: Membership Slate leaflets, September 1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Local referendum on Bylaws, International referendum on 50 cent dues increase: campaign leaflets and drafts, December 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Unit referedum on the "$6 Question": Correspondence, November 1981, January 1982 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Unit referendum on the "$6 Question": Leaflets, November 1981, January 1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Secretary-Treasurer election: Membership Slate leaflets, March 1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Secretary-Treasurer election: Membership Slate complaint, correspondence and notes, financial records, March 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Secretary-Treasurer election: Membership Slate drafts of campaign literature, speeches, and newsstories, March 1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Secretary-Treasurer election: Democratic Coalition and Fiscal Integrity candidate leaflets, March 1982 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- The Newspaper Guild delegate election, and referendum re-run of 1980 local election: Membership Slate leaflets, May 1982 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- The Newspaper Guild delegate election, and referendum re-run of 1980 local election: Referendum Committee and Democratic Coalition leaflets, May 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Referendum on 1980 local election re-run: Membership Slate campaign literature drafts, notes, correspondence, May 1982 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- 1980 local election re-run: (Betsy Wade's?) notes, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- 1980 local election re-run: correspondence and memos, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- 1980 local election re-run: legal documents and related correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Supervised re-run of 1980 local election: Membership Slate campaign leaflets, September 29, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Supervised re-run of 1980 local election: Democratic Coalition leaflets, September 29, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- (New York Times) unit referendum on unit clarification: leaflets, October 7-October 8, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- (New York Times) unit election: Membership Slate campaign literature, financial documents, and correspondence, October 14-October 15, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- (New York Times) unit election: Democratic Coalition and Rank and File Coalition campaign literature, October 14-October 15, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- New York Times unit Welfare, Pension, Scholarship Fund trustee dispute: leaflets, correspondence, 1982/1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- New York Times unit Welfare, Pension, Scholarship Fund trustee dispute: legal documents, correspondence, negotiation notes, 1982/1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Local election-Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer: Drafts of Membership Slate campaign literature, December 1982 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Local election-Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer: Membership Slate leaflets, December 1982 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Local election-Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer: Democratic Coalition leaflets, December 1982 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Local election-Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer: Membership Slate correspondence, December 1982 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Local 3 staff raises dispute: Leaflets, June 1983 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty Bylaw Referendum: Membership Slate leaflets, December 1983 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty Bylaw Referendum: Democratic Coalition and allies leaflets, December 1983 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Radio Free Europe dispute: correspondence, 1967; 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Radio Free Europe dispute: legal and related documents, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- New York Times unit clarification/contract extension referendum: leaflets, January 1984 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- New York Times unit welfare benefits referndum: leaflets, March 1984 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- (New York Times) unit election: campaign literature, October 1984 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Miscellaneous referendum and election campaign literature and correspondence, various dates (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Miscellaneous Membership Slate financial documents, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Election protests and appeals: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Miscellaneous Membership Slate correspondence, memos and notes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- International Election Committee and Caucus/committee for Responsible Leadership: memos, correspondence, notes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Tally sheets and ballots, 1967; 1978-1985 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Petitions and petition forms, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Rules for nomination of candidates and conduct of September 29, 1982 supervised election re-run (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Rules for International Referendum on New Dues Schedule, December 1, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Rules for Special Referendum (December 1983) on Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty unit Munich division dues and local bylaws revision (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Rules for election of International Vice President and Vice President for various regions, 1979, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Rules for nomination of local office, 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Rules for nomination and election of local officers and executive committee, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Rules for nomination and election of Executive Vice President and Secretary Treasurer, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Rules for nomination and election of unit officers, 1977-1984 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Rules for nomination and election of delegates and alternates to the conventions of The Newspaper Guild and New York State Allied Printing Trades, 1967; 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Rules for nomination and election of delegates to Special The Newspaper Guild Convention, January 1983 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Rules for Trustee Dispute referendum (scheduled for April 28-April 29, 1983, but cancelled) (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Rules for international referendum on 50 cent dues increase, December 17-December 18, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Reports of audits, budgets, notes (1 of 4), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Reports of audits, budgets, notes (2 of 4), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Reports of audits, budgets, notes (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Reports of audits, budgets, notes (4 of 4), 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Legal bills, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Frontpage: Letters to the Editor, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Frontpage: President's Column, various drafts, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Frontpage; Local 3 Bulletin, Union Times: drafts of stories, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Resignation cases: Brief, decisions, complaint, National Labor Regulation Board documents, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Local 3 Staff contracts (between OPEIU abd Local 3) and contract negotiation correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Staff contracts (between Local Representatives Guild and Local 3, and between Federation of Guild Representatives and Local 3) and related materials, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Correspondence regarding Local 3 staff performance, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Betsy Wade-notes, strategies, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Betsy Wade-speeches, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Betsy Wade-packing lists, not dated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Tri-Council (Great Lakes, Midwest, and Southern District Councils): Minutes, agendas, reports, notices, 1979, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Middle Atlantic District Council: Minutes, agenda, and reports for locals, financial reports, notes, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Middle Atlantic District Council: Correspondence, reports on Local 3, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Middle Atlantic District Council: Attendance sheets, delegates, and alternates lists, 1980-1982; not dated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Midwest District Council: Minutes, agendas, reports from locals, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Great Lakes, New England, and Western District Councils: Minutes, reports from locals, 1978, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Bylaws, various district councils, not dated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development and The Newspaper Guild programs: contracts, budgets, notes, 1976, 1978, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Newspaper clippings on American Institute for Free Labor Development-Central Intelligence Agency connection, 1966, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Newspaper clippings on American Institute for Free Labor Development-Central Intelligence Agency connection, 1978-1981; not dated (Box 6, Folder 25)
- (Foreign Affairs) Correspondence, memos, statements, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- General membership meeting, Local 3, March 6, 1967: Reports on, speech given at (Box 6, Folder 27)
- The Newspaper Guild convention proceedings (partial), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Anti-American Institute for Free Labor Development packet for The Newspaper Guild convention: originals and copy, June 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Anti-American Institute for Free Labor Development packet for The Newspaper Guild convention: drafts and research notes, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- 1979 The Newspaper Guild convention documents (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 1980 The Newspaper Guild convention: resolutions, reports (Box 6, Folder 32)
- (Foreign Affairs) Correspondence, memos, reports, notes (1 of 3), 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 33)